You really thought you’ve been scared?
Ghostland is a horror, mystery, thriller film directed by Pascal Laugier.
A mother of two inherits a home from her aunt.
On the first night in the new home she is confronted with
murderous intruders and fights for her daughters’ lives.
Sixteen years later the daughters reunite at the house,
and that is when things get strange...
Beth, played by Crystal Reed.
Pauline, played by Mylène Farmer.
Vera, played by Anastasia Phillips.
Young Beth, played by Emilia Jones.
Young Vera, played by Taylor Hickson.
Fat Man, played by Rob Archer.
Ghostland (also known as Incident in a Ghostland) is a 2018
psychological horror film  written and directed by Pascal Laugier.
Ghostland was shown in competition at the Festival international du film fantastique
de Gérardmer, where it won three awards, including the Grand Prize.
The film is a co-production between Canada and France.
The film explores themes of insanity,
hallucination, torture, reality vs fantasy.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.